final topic1 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":" The teacher said that we .......... harder on our pronunciation.","trueAnswer":"should work","falseAnswer1":"have worked","falseAnwser2":"working","falseAnwer3":"work"},{"id":"2","question":"The train couldn’t run fast .................... snow.","trueAnswer":"because of","falseAnswer1":"because","falseAnwser2":"if","falseAnwer3":"so"},{"id":"3","question":"Don’t let children .......... in the kitchen.","trueAnswer":"play","falseAnswer1":"playing","falseAnwser2":"to play","falseAnwer3":"played"},{"id":"4","question":"Which songs do they often sing ............. Christmas?","trueAnswer":"at","falseAnswer1":"on","falseAnwser2":"in","falseAnwer3":"of"},{"id":"5","question":"She was ............ because of her bad result.","trueAnswer":"unhappy","falseAnswer1":"happy","falseAnwser2":"happily","falseAnwer3":"unhappily"},{"id":"6","question":"She has .............. provided a picnic lunch for us.","trueAnswer":"kindly","falseAnswer1":"kind","falseAnwser2":"unkind","falseAnwer3":"kindness"},{"id":"7","question":"We ..................... this car if it is expensive.","trueAnswer":"won’t buy","falseAnswer1":"haven’t bought","falseAnwser2":"didn’t buy","falseAnwer3":"wouldn’t buy"},{"id":"8","question":"If he is careful, he .......... get good marks.","trueAnswer":"will","falseAnswer1":"must","falseAnwser2":"could","falseAnwer3":"would"},{"id":"9","question":"Is he really ................ that you can’t come there.","trueAnswer":"disappointed","falseAnswer1":"disappointing","falseAnwser2":"to disappoint","falseAnwer3":"disappoint"},{"id":"10","question":"I think most children are creative enough to write .......... poems.","trueAnswer":"beautiful","falseAnswer1":"beautifully","falseAnwser2":"beauty","falseAnwer3":"beautify"},{"id":"11","question":"It is necessary ............ forests.","trueAnswer":"to protect","falseAnswer1":"protect","falseAnwser2":"protected","falseAnwer3":"protecting"},{"id":"12","question":"They made their living by .......... fish in the ocean every day.","trueAnswer":"catching","falseAnswer1":"catch","falseAnwser2":"to catch","falseAnwer3":"caught"},{"id":"13","question":"I suggest .............. to the movies.","trueAnswer":"going","falseAnswer1":"go","falseAnwser2":"to go","falseAnwer3":"went"},{"id":"14","question":"I have sent you a lot of letters but you have never been .....................","trueAnswer":"responsive","falseAnswer1":"respond","falseAnwser2":"response","falseAnwer3":"responsively"},{"id":"15","question":"The cost of ............ is very high in big cities.","trueAnswer":"living","falseAnswer1":"life","falseAnwser2":"live","falseAnwer3":"lived"},{"id":"16","question":"The next stage in the development of television is ...............TV.","trueAnswer":"interactive","falseAnswer1":"interact","falseAnwser2":"interaction","falseAnwer3":"interactively"},{"id":"17","question":"By learning English, you can get access to the world’s ................","trueAnswer":"development","falseAnswer1":"develop","falseAnwser2":"developed","falseAnwer3":"developing"},{"id":"18","question":"Hurry up, or you won’t ....................... the last bus.","trueAnswer":"catch","falseAnswer1":"miss","falseAnwser2":"take","falseAnwer3":"go"},{"id":"19","question":"He can swim and ................. can I.","trueAnswer":"so","falseAnswer1":"to","falseAnwser2":"too","falseAnwer3":"such"},{"id":"20","question":"Let’s wait .............. the rain stops.","trueAnswer":"until","falseAnswer1":"before","falseAnwser2":"after","falseAnwer3":"when"}]';
final topic2 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"“How many pages…………… so far?”","trueAnswer":"have you studied","falseAnswer1":" did you study","falseAnwser2":" do you study","falseAnwer3":"had you studied"},{"id":"2","question":"We are too late. The plane …………… off ten minutes ago","trueAnswer":"took","falseAnswer1":"has taken","falseAnwser2":"had taken","falseAnwer3":"was taken"},{"id":"3","question":"“What a lovely boat!” “I ……………half a year building this boat.”","trueAnswer":"spent","falseAnswer1":"spend","falseAnwser2":"spending","falseAnwer3":"have spent"},{"id":"4","question":"How …………since we …………school?","trueAnswer":"have you been/ left","falseAnswer1":"are you/ left","falseAnwser2":"have you been/ have left","falseAnwer3":"were you/ left"},{"id":"5","question":"I think John …………..tomorrow.","trueAnswer":"will come","falseAnswer1":"would come","falseAnwser2":"come","falseAnwer3":"comes"},{"id":"6","question":"After he ------------ his driving test he bought a car.","trueAnswer":"had passed","falseAnswer1":"pass","falseAnwser2":"passed","falseAnwer3":"passing"},{"id":"7","question":"When I got to the office, I ----------- that I had forgot to lock the door.","trueAnswer":"realized","falseAnswer1":"had realized","falseAnwser2":"realize","falseAnwer3":" have realized"},{"id":"8","question":"When she was 21 she -------------- across the United States","trueAnswer":"drove","falseAnswer1":"drive","falseAnwser2":"driven","falseAnwer3":"was driving"},{"id":"9","question":"He often ------------ so nervous before his exams","trueAnswer":"feels","falseAnswer1":"felt","falseAnwser2":"was feeling","falseAnwer3":"had felt"},{"id":"10","question":"How long have you ------------- he was a liar","trueAnswer":"known","falseAnswer1":"been knowing","falseAnwser2":" knew","falseAnwer3":" know"},{"id":"11","question":" I’m sorry. I don’t understand what -----------------.","trueAnswer":"you’re saying","falseAnswer1":"you say","falseAnwser2":"you will say","falseAnwer3":"you would say"},{"id":"12","question":"------------- to the radio when you get up everyday?","trueAnswer":"Do you listen","falseAnswer1":"Are you listening","falseAnwser2":"Was you listening","falseAnwer3":"Did you listen"},{"id":"13","question":" My sweetheart --------------- smoking next week","trueAnswer":"is going to give up ","falseAnswer1":"will give up","falseAnwser2":"give up","falseAnwer3":"gave up"},{"id":"14","question":"There is no red wine? I -------------- white, then","trueAnswer":"will have","falseAnswer1":"am going to have","falseAnwser2":" have","falseAnwer3":" am having"},{"id":"15","question":" When the phone rang she ------------ a letter","trueAnswer":"was writing","falseAnswer1":"writes","falseAnwser2":"will write","falseAnwer3":"has written"},{"id":"16","question":". As the sun ------------ I decided to go out.","trueAnswer":"was shining","falseAnswer1":"shines","falseAnwser2":"has shone","falseAnwer3":"shine"},{"id":"17","question":" I------------- your uncle tomorrow, so I’ll give him your note.","trueAnswer":"am going to see","falseAnswer1":" have seen","falseAnwser2":"shall have seen","falseAnwer3":"see"},{"id":"18","question":"-------------- study hard when you were at school?","trueAnswer":"Did you have to","falseAnswer1":"Must you","falseAnwser2":" Had you","falseAnwer3":"Were you"},{"id":"19","question":" She is tired because she ------------- all day","trueAnswer":"has been studying","falseAnswer1":"is studied","falseAnwser2":"had been studying","falseAnwer3":" studied"},{"id":"20","question":" Has your teacher ever ------------ angry with you?","trueAnswer":"got","falseAnswer1":"get","falseAnwser2":"getting","falseAnwer3":"gets"}]';
final topic3 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":" He ----------","trueAnswer":"will be here soon","falseAnswer1":"will here be soon","falseAnwser2":"will be soon here","falseAnwer3":"be soon will ere"},{"id":"2","question":"They------------ to the theatre twice so far this month.","trueAnswer":"have been","falseAnswer1":" went","falseAnwser2":"go","falseAnwer3":"are going"},{"id":"3","question":"My daughter ------------- university last June","trueAnswer":"left","falseAnswer1":" has left","falseAnwser2":"leaves","falseAnwer3":"was leaving"},{"id":"4","question":"He hates his boss so he ------------- his job","trueAnswer":"is leaving","falseAnswer1":"leaves","falseAnwser2":" has left","falseAnwer3":"left"},{"id":"5","question":"While the waiter was picking up the broken plates, he ---------- his finger","trueAnswer":" cut","falseAnswer1":"was cutting","falseAnwser2":"had cut","falseAnwer3":"cuts"},{"id":"6","question":"Pam was always afraid------------ cooking.","trueAnswer":"of","falseAnswer1":"to","falseAnwser2":"for","falseAnwer3":"at"},{"id":"7","question":"When Joe was at school, he was very good----- ---- running.","trueAnswer":"at","falseAnswer1":" in","falseAnwser2":" for","falseAnwer3":" to"},{"id":"8","question":"We’ve been thinking ------- moving house","trueAnswer":"of","falseAnswer1":"in","falseAnwser2":" to","falseAnwer3":"on"},{"id":"9","question":"On his third try, he succeeded------------ passing his driving test","trueAnswer":" in","falseAnswer1":"at","falseAnwser2":"on","falseAnwer3":"to"},{"id":"10","question":"I’m fed up -------- working, I need a holiday","trueAnswer":"with","falseAnswer1":"to","falseAnwser2":" in","falseAnwer3":" for"},{"id":"11","question":" I’m frightened----------- spiders, they terrify me","trueAnswer":"of","falseAnswer1":"in","falseAnwser2":" of","falseAnwer3":"for"},{"id":"12","question":"They went ----------- holiday yesterday","trueAnswer":"on","falseAnswer1":"in","falseAnwser2":"at","falseAnwer3":" during"},{"id":"13","question":"She’s always talking --------- the phone","trueAnswer":"on","falseAnswer1":" in","falseAnwser2":"at","falseAnwer3":"over"},{"id":"14","question":"John went red after sitting----------- the sun all day","trueAnswer":"in","falseAnswer1":"at","falseAnwser2":" on","falseAnwer3":"by"},{"id":"15","question":" He didn’t want cash, so I paid the bill----------- credit card","trueAnswer":"by","falseAnswer1":"with","falseAnwser2":"in","falseAnwer3":"on"},{"id":"16","question":"Jim doesn’t enjoy-------------- sport","trueAnswer":"doing","falseAnswer1":"to do","falseAnwser2":"do","falseAnwer3":"to doing"},{"id":"17","question":" We are trying ----------- money to buy a house","trueAnswer":"to save","falseAnswer1":" saving","falseAnwser2":"save","falseAnwer3":" saves"},{"id":"18","question":"Would you like something-----------?","trueAnswer":"to drink","falseAnswer1":" drink","falseAnwser2":"drinking","falseAnwer3":"drinks"},{"id":"19","question":"Our teacher doesn’t let us -------------- gum in class.","trueAnswer":"chew","falseAnswer1":" chewing","falseAnwser2":"to chew","falseAnwer3":"chews"},{"id":"20","question":"It’s hard ------------ my father as a child.","trueAnswer":"to imagine","falseAnswer1":"imagines","falseAnwser2":"imagining","falseAnwer3":"imagine"}]';
final topic4 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"The mausoleum is ................. by Thien Thu mountain, two towering columns and a vast expanse of ","trueAnswer":"fed","falseAnswer1":"water.","falseAnwser2":"feed","falseAnwer3":"feeding "},{"id":"2","question":"Put plants ............... a window so that they will get enough light.","trueAnswer":"next to ","falseAnswer1":"near to ","falseAnwser2":"near of ","falseAnwer3":"nearly"},{"id":"3","question":"Employers often require that candidates have not only a degree .............","trueAnswer":"but also two-year experience","falseAnswer1":"but two years experience","falseAnwser2":"also two years experience","falseAnwer3":"but more two years experience"},{"id":"4","question":"Richard Nixon had been a lawyer and ............... before he entered politics.","trueAnswer":"the Navy had him as an officer","falseAnswer1":"served in the Navy as an officer ","falseAnwser2":"0","falseAnwer3":"did service in the Navy as an officer"},{"id":"5","question":"If one of the participants in a conversation wonders ............... no real communication has taken place.","trueAnswer":"what the other person said","falseAnswer1":"what said the other person ","falseAnwser2":"what did the other person say","falseAnwer3":"what was the other person saying"},{"id":"6","question":"The salary of a bus driver is much higher ................ ","trueAnswer":"than that of a teacher","falseAnswer1":"in comparison with the salary of a teacher","falseAnwser2":"than a teacher","falseAnwer3":"to compare as a teacher"},{"id":"7","question":"Professional people expect ............... when it is necessary to cancel an appointment.","trueAnswer":"you to call them","falseAnswer1":"that you would call them","falseAnwser2":"your calling them","falseAnwer3":"that you are calling them"},{"id":"8","question":"Sedimentary rocks are formed below the surface of the earth ............... very high temperatures and pressures.","trueAnswer":"where there are ","falseAnswer1":"0","falseAnwser2":"where are there ","falseAnwer3":"there are where"},{"id":"9","question":"Farmers look forward to ............... every summer. ","trueAnswer":"participating in the county fairs","falseAnswer1":"participate in the county fairs","falseAnwser2":"be participating in the county fairs","falseAnwer3":"have participated in the county fairs"},{"id":"10","question":"Clipper ships were the swiftest sailing ships that …………………. to sea and the most beautiful.","trueAnswer":"were ever put","falseAnswer1":"ever were put","falseAnwser2":"were ever putted ","falseAnwer3":"ever were putted"},{"id":"11","question":"The ships had their days of …………………. in the 1840s and 1850s.","trueAnswer":"glory ","falseAnswer1":"Glorious","falseAnwser2":"glorify","falseAnwer3":"gloriously"},{"id":"12","question":"Tea loses its flavor quickly …………………… in the hold of a vessel.","trueAnswer":"when stored ","falseAnswer1":"when storing","falseAnwser2":"stored  ","falseAnwer3":"storing"},{"id":"13","question":"Earl was one of the first American artists …………………. landscapes.","trueAnswer":"to paint","falseAnswer1":"Painting","falseAnwser2":"Painted","falseAnwer3":"for painting "},{"id":"14","question":"The crime rate has continued to rise in American cities despite efforts on the part of both government and private citizens to curb ................","trueAnswer":"it","falseAnswer1":"them ","falseAnwser2":"him ","falseAnwer3":"its"},{"id":"15","question":"In 1778, he ……………… to London to study with Benjamin West for four years.","trueAnswer":"went","falseAnswer1":"has gone ","falseAnwser2":"had gone ","falseAnwer3":"would go "},{"id":"16","question":"No one has been able to satisfactorily explain how or ………… The Moon sporadically sparks.","trueAnswer":"why","falseAnswer1":"when","falseAnwser2":"what ","falseAnwer3":"which"},{"id":"17","question":"The basic fiber-optics system is called a fiberscope, ………… Consists of two bundles of fibers.","trueAnswer":"Which","falseAnswer1":"in which ","falseAnwser2":"where   ","falseAnwer3":"what"},{"id":"18","question":"Physicians can look into the lungs, heart and other areas that were formerly…………….. to them.","trueAnswer":"inaccessible","falseAnswer1":"Accessibly","falseAnwser2":"Access","falseAnwer3":"Accessible"},{"id":"19","question":" ............... his highly individual conceptions of music and chaos, John Cage became a leading figure in avant-garde music.","trueAnswer":"Due to","falseAnswer1":"Such was ","falseAnwser2":"Because from ","falseAnwer3":"That"},{"id":"20","question":"Sanford Meisner ............... the Neighborhood Playhouse in New York City.","trueAnswer":"founded and directed","falseAnswer1":"founding and directing","falseAnwser2":"who founded and directed","falseAnwer3":"in finding and directing"}]';
final topic5 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"Experiments in the sonic imaging of moving objects ............... in both the United States and Europe well before the Second World War. ","trueAnswer":"had been conducted","falseAnswer1":"were conducting","falseAnwser2":"have been conducted ","falseAnwer3":"being conducted"},{"id":"2","question":"............... billions and billions of stars exist in the vast space beyond our Milky Way galaxy.","trueAnswer":"It is estimated that","falseAnswer1":"That is estimated ","falseAnwser2":"An estimate that ","falseAnwer3":"That the estimate "},{"id":"3","question":"............... gene-bearing bodies within the nuclei of living organisms.","trueAnswer":"Chromosomes are","falseAnswer1":"Chromosomes","falseAnwser2":"Chromosomes that are ","falseAnwer3":"Chromosomes while they are"},{"id":"4","question":". Abner Doubleday, ..............., was credited with the invention of baseball in 1839.","trueAnswer":"a Union army general","falseAnswer1":"which became a Union army general ","falseAnwser2":"whose were a Union army general","falseAnwer3":"My a Union army general"},{"id":"5. ","question":"............... photosynthesis were to stop, life would disappear from the planet Earth relatively quickly.","trueAnswer":"If","falseAnswer1":"However ","falseAnwser2":"Although","falseAnwer3":"For"},{"id":"6","question":"Each fiber in the bundle …………….. only a tiny fraction of the total image.","trueAnswer":"Transmits","falseAnswer1":"transmitted ","falseAnwser2":"to transmit","falseAnwer3":"transmit"},{"id":"7","question":" Antonio Gaudi, architect of Barcelona is Holy Family Church, died before seeing ............... the structure.","trueAnswer":"the completion of","falseAnswer1":"completing of","falseAnwser2":"their completing of","falseAnwer3":"on completion of "},{"id":"8","question":"This is the factory ................................. at work. ","trueAnswer":"where they are ","falseAnswer1":"they are","falseAnswer2":"where are","falseAnwser3":"in where they are"},{"id":"9","question":"America is first globe maker was James Wilson, who ................... and blacksmith in his earlier life.","trueAnswer":"had been a farmer ","falseAnswer1":"a farmer had been ","falseAnswer2":"farming","falseAnwser3":"being a farmer"},{"id":"10","question":"Napoleon ................... the West Indian island of Santo Domingo in 1801.","trueAnswer":"Attacked","falseAnwser1":"is attacking","falseAnswer2":"has attracted ","falseAnwser3":"attacking"},{"id":"11","question":"Modern industrial methods have supplanted individual crafts, ...................","trueAnswer":"making blacksmiths,","falseAnswer1":"make blacksmiths,","falseAnwser2":"made blacksmiths,","falseAnwer3":"making them blacksmiths,"},{"id":"12","question":"Not only knowledge and skills, but also attitudes ................... in school for students `s future need to be cultivated","trueAnswer":"adjustment to society.","falseAnswer1":"when cultivated ","falseAnwser2":"cultivated","falseAnwer3":"which need to be cultivated "},{"id":"13","question":"On Mercator`s maps, the far northern and southern polar regions are....................","trueAnswer":"greatly exaggerated in area. ","falseAnswer1":"exaggerating greatly in area.","falseAnwser2":"greatly exaggerate in area.","falseAnwer3":"great exaggeration in area."},{"id":"14","question":"On the slope of Long`s Peak in Colorado ................... the ruin of a gigantic tree.","trueAnswer":"lies ","falseAnswer1":"that lies","falseAnwser2":"where lies ","falseAnwer3":"lie"},{"id":"15 ","question":". ................... in Shanghai than in any other city in China.","trueAnswer":"More people live ","falseAnswer1":"It has more people ","falseAnwser2":"More living people","falseAnwer3":"It has more people "},{"id":"16","question":"The earth spins on its axis and ................... 23 hours, 56 minutes and 4.09","trueAnswer":"needs. ","falseAnswer1":" need   ","falseAnwser2":"needed ","falseAnwer3":"needing "},{"id":"17","question":" ................... on the environment for the gratification of its needs.","trueAnswer":"Every organism depends ","falseAnswer1":"Each organism to depend ","falseAnwser2":"All organisms depending","falseAnwer3":"Many organisms can depend"},{"id":"18","question":"Of Charles Dickens` many novels, expectations perhaps ................... to many readers.","trueAnswer":"the most satisfying one","falseAnswer1":"most satisfying one","falseAnwser2":"more than satisfying one ","falseAnwer3":"the more satisfying than"},{"id":"19","question":"..................., the nation`s capital remained in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.","trueAnswer":"While Washington, D.C., was being designed ","falseAnswer1":"While designing Washington, D.C. ","falseAnwser2":"Washington, D.C., was designed","falseAnwer3":"Washington, D.C., designed"},{"id":"20 ","question":"Children learn primarily by ................... the world around them.","trueAnswer":"direct physical experience of","falseAnswer1":"experiencing directly of ","falseAnwser2":"experience direct","falseAnwer3":"directly physical experience "}]';
final toppicVC1 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"The house was burgled while the family was _______ in a card game.","trueAnswer":"absorbed","falseAnswer1":"buried ","falseAnwser2":"busy ","falseAnwer3":"helping "},{"id":"2","question":"I am sorry that I can’t _______ your invitation.","trueAnswer":"accept ","falseAnswer1":"take","falseAnwser2":"except  ","falseAnwer3":"agree"},{"id":"3 ","question":"______ what he says, he wasn’t even there when the crime was committed. ","trueAnswer":"According to  ","falseAnswer1":"Following ","falseAnwser2":"Hearing ","falseAnwer3":"meaning "},{"id":"4","question":" He has impressed his employers considerably and ______ he is soon to be promoted.  ","trueAnswer":"accordingly","falseAnswer1":"nevertheless ","falseAnwser2":"yet","falseAnwer3":"eventually "},{"id":"5 ","question":"He gave his listeners a vivid ______ of his journey through Peru.  ","trueAnswer":"account ","falseAnswer1":"tale  ","falseAnwser2":"communication ","falseAnwer3":"plot "},{"id":"6. ","question":"Will you be taking my precious experience into _______ when you fix my salary? ","trueAnswer":"account","falseAnswer1":"possession ","falseAnwser2":"mind    ","falseAnwer3":"scale "},{"id":"7","question":"The policeman stopped him when he was driving home and _______ him of speeding.  ","trueAnswer":"accused ","falseAnswer1":"charged ","falseAnwser2":"blamed ","falseAnwer3":"arrested "},{"id":"8.","question":"His stomach began to _______ because of the bad food he had eaten. ","trueAnswer":" ache ","falseAnswer1":"pain ","falseAnwser2":"harm","falseAnwer3":"be hurt"},{"id":"9","question":" If you _____ money to mine, we shall have enough.  ","trueAnswer":"Add","falseAnswer1":"combine ","falseAnwser2":"unite ","falseAnwer3":"bank "},{"id":"10","question":"He was full of _______ for her bravery.  ","trueAnswer":"admiration","falseAnswer1":"energy  ","falseAnwser2":"surprise ","falseAnwer3":"pride "},{"id":"11","question":"This ticket _____ one person to the show. ","trueAnswer":"admits","falseAnswer1":"permits ","falseAnwser2":"enters ","falseAnwer3":"delivers "},{"id":"12","question":"The cow had lost its own calf. but the farmer persuaded it to _______ one whose mother had ","trueAnswer":"undertake ","falseAnswer1":"died.","falseAnwser2":"choose","falseAnwer3":"collect "},{"id":"13","question":"If we _______ the plan you suggest, we are more likely to be successful. ","trueAnswer":"adopt","falseAnswer1":"elect ","falseAnwser2":"command  ","falseAnwer3":"vote          "},{"id":"14","question":"Science has made great _____ during the past 30 years.  ","trueAnswer":"advances  ","falseAnswer1":"motions","falseAnwser2":"advantages ","falseAnwer3":"opportunities "},{"id":"15","question":"He was a much older tennis player but he had the great ______ of experience. ","trueAnswer":"advantage ","falseAnswer1":"deal ","falseAnwser2":"value ","falseAnwer3":"profit "},{"id":"16.","question":"I had quite ______ on my way to work this morning.  ","trueAnswer":"an adventure ","falseAnswer1":"an experiment   ","falseAnwser2":"a happening ","falseAnwer3":"an affair "},{"id":"17","question":"He always studies the ______ in the paper ashe wants to find a good second-hand car.  ","trueAnswer":"advertisements ","falseAnswer1":"publicity ","falseAnwser2":"announcements ","falseAnwer3":"publication "},{"id":"18","question":"On my present salary, I just can’t________ a car which costs over 3.000.  ","trueAnswer":"afford ","falseAnswer1":"pretend ","falseAnwser2":"elect ","falseAnwer3":"adopt "},{"id":"19","question":"The girl’s father _____ to buy her a car if she passed her examination.","trueAnswer":"agreed     ","falseAnswer1":"admitted ","falseAnwser2":"accepted ","falseAnwer3":"            approved "},{"id":"20","question":"They are twins and look very _______.  ","trueAnswer":"alike ","falseAnswer1":"same ","falseAnwser2":"likely ","falseAnwer3":"identical "}]';
final toppicVC2 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"The charity aims to _____ food and shelter for underprivileged in the remote areas of the country","trueAnswer":"provide ","falseAnswer1":"present ","falseAnwser2":"assist ","falseAnwer3":"offer "},{"id":"2","question":" We need to promote a lifestyle that is _____ to the environment. ","trueAnswer":"friendly ","falseAnswer1":"friend ","falseAnwser2":"friendship ","falseAnwer3":"friendliness "},{"id":"3","question":"At school, children learn a lot of _____ such as maths, biology, history, geography and English","trueAnswer":"subjects ","falseAnswer1":"topics ","falseAnwser2":"lessons ","falseAnwer3":"objects "},{"id":" 4","question":"The child that we caught _____ was made to stand in the corner of the classroom","trueAnswer":"misbehaving ","falseAnswer1":"misbehavior ","falseAnwser2":"misbehave ","falseAnwer3":"behaving "},{"id":"5","question":"Make sure you ______ up the data on your computer, because you might get a virus","trueAnswer":"copy ","falseAnswer1":"back ","falseAnwser2":"store ","falseAnwer3":"save "},{"id":"6","question":" Population explosion seems to surpass the ability of the earth to ______ the demand for food.","trueAnswer":"meet ","falseAnswer1":"make ","falseAnwser2":"need ","falseAnwer3":"have"},{"id":"7","question":" My parents will have celebrated 30 years of ______ by next week.","trueAnswer":"marriage ","falseAnswer1":"marry ","falseAnwser2":"married ","falseAnwer3":"marriageable "},{"id":"8","question":"The singer was ______ on the piano by her sister. ","trueAnswer":"played ","falseAnswer1":"discarded ","falseAnwser2":"accompanied ","falseAnwer3":"performed "},{"id":"9","question":"He did not share his secrets with other people, but he ______ in her. ","trueAnswer":"confessed ","falseAnswer1":"concealed ","falseAnwser2":"confided ","falseAnwer3":"consented "},{"id":"10","question":"Great ______ should be given to the conservation of endangered species. ","trueAnswer":"priority ","falseAnswer1":"diversity ","falseAnwser2":"opportunity ","falseAnwer3":"condition "},{"id":"11","question":"They were among the first companies to exploit the ______ of the Internet","trueAnswer":"Potential","falseAnswer1":"prospect ","falseAnwser2":"possibility ","falseAnwer3":"ability"},{"id":"12","question":"She pays an enormous insurance premium on the family heirloom, her most _______ possession","trueAnswer":"priceless ","falseAnswer1":"valueless ","falseAnwser2":"honourable ","falseAnwer3":"treasured "},{"id":"13","question":" She____________her success to hard work. ","trueAnswer":"devoted ","falseAnswer1":"described ","falseAnwser2":"blamed ","falseAnwer3":"ascribed "},{"id":"14","question":"It’s funny you should say that. I’ve just had the________ thought. ","trueAnswer":"similar ","falseAnswer1":"like ","falseAnwser2":"identical ","falseAnwer3":"alike "},{"id":"15","question":"The dead man’s widow said he had had a/an ____that he would be killed in an accident. ","trueAnswer":"presentiment ","falseAnswer1":"knowledge ","falseAnwser2":"experience ","falseAnwer3":"warning "},{"id":"16","question":" I’ve got lots of __________________ but only a few really good friends. ","trueAnswer":"accpuaintances ","falseAnswer1":"neighbors ","falseAnwser2":"best mates ","falseAnwer3":"partners "},{"id":"17","question":"The marriage pattern of parents plays an extremely important role in ___________marriage roles of children. ","trueAnswer":"socializing ","falseAnswer1":"socialist ","falseAnwser2":"socialism ","falseAnwer3":"social "},{"id":"18","question":" As soon as the suppliers arrive, they will be ______________to the starving people in the flooded areas","trueAnswer":"distributed ","falseAnswer1":"attributed ","falseAnwser2":"contributed ","falseAnwer3":"submitted "},{"id":"19","question":"The top tourist _________________ in Vietnam, Ha Long Bay features thousands of islands, each topped with thick jungle vegetation, forming a spectacular seascape of limestone pillars. ","trueAnswer":"attraction ","falseAnswer1":"attractiveness ","falseAnwser2":"attractive ","falseAnwer3":"attract "},{"id":" 20","question":"Remember to bring with you your school certificate and letters of _________from your teachers or your previous employers when you come to the interview. ","trueAnswer":"Recommendation ","falseAnswer1":"assighment ","falseAnwser2":"advertisement ","falseAnwer3":"invitation"}]';
final toppicVC3 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"Many plant and animal species are now on the ___________ of extinction","trueAnswer":"Margin","falseAnswer1":"Verge","falseAnwser2":"danger ","falseAnwer3":"border"},{"id":" 2","question":" People have used coal and oil to ______electricity for a long time","trueAnswer":"bred ","falseAnswer1":"raise ","falseAnwser2":"cultivate ","falseAnwer3":"generate "},{"id":"3","question":"Nowadays, most students use ________ calculators in their studies and examinations. ","trueAnswer":"electrical ","falseAnswer1":"electricity ","falseAnwser2":"electric ","falseAnwer3":"electronic "},{"id":"4","question":"The Mountainview Hotel offers its guests a ________ buffet breakfast every morning. ","trueAnswer":"valuable ","falseAnswer1":"situated","falseAnwser2":"dependent ","falseAnwer3":"complimentary "},{"id":"5 ","question":"Water is ________ of two elements: hydrogen and oxygen","trueAnswer":"consisted ","falseAnswer1":"composed ","falseAnwser2":"making ","falseAnwer3":"comprising "},{"id":"6","question":" I want to ________ a table at the Bamboo Restaurant","trueAnswer":"maintain ","falseAnswer1":"manage ","falseAnwser2":"reserve ","falseAnwer3":"allow "},{"id":"7 ","question":"Mr.Pike provided us with an____ guide to the full-time and part-time programson offer to a range of candidates drawn from schools and colleges","trueAnswer":"inform ","falseAnswer1":"informative ","falseAnwser2":"informed ","falseAnwer3":"information"},{"id":" 8 ","question":"It was just a friendly get-together. Everyone was wearing_____ clothes. No one needed to be well-dressed","trueAnswer":"Formal","falseAnswer1":"unimportant ","falseAnwser2":"casual ","falseAnwer3":"unfriendly "},{"id":"9 ","question":"Someone who is ______ is hopeful about the future or the success of something in particular","trueAnswer":"powerfull ","falseAnswer1":"optimistic ","falseAnwser2":"stagnant ","falseAnwer3":"pessimistic "},{"id":"10","question":" _________ candidates are likely to succeed in job interviews. ","trueAnswer":"nervous ","falseAnswer1":"self-confident ","falseAnwser2":"self-conscious ","falseAnwer3":"self-doubt "},{"id":"11 ","question":"There are several places where residents face the threat of _______every day","trueAnswer":"terrorist ","falseAnswer1":"terrorism ","falseAnwser2":"terrorize ","falseAnwer3":"terror "},{"id":"12 ","question":"They are always_______ of what their children do. ","trueAnswer":"support ","falseAnswer1":"supporting ","falseAnwser2":"supportive ","falseAnwer3":"supportively "},{"id":"13","question":" Women in some parts of the world are still struggling for_______ job opportunities to men. ","trueAnswer":"equal ","falseAnswer1":"various ","falseAnwser2":"suitable ","falseAnwer3":"legal "},{"id":"14 ","question":"The manager_______ his temper with the employees and shouted at them","trueAnswer":"had ","falseAnswer1":"lost ","falseAnwser2":"took ","falseAnwer3":"kept "},{"id":"15 ","question":"All nations should_______ hands to work out a plan to solve the problem of global warming. ","trueAnswer":"join ","falseAnswer1":"hold ","falseAnwser2":"shake ","falseAnwer3":"lend "},{"id":"16 ","question":"The shop assistant is ready to ________ me a helping hand. She is very nice. ","trueAnswer":"take ","falseAnswer1":"lend ","falseAnwser2":"offer ","falseAnwer3":"get "},{"id":"17","question":":I’d like to ________ this old car for a new model but I can’t afford it.","trueAnswer":"convert ","falseAnswer1":"exchange ","falseAnwser2":"replace ","falseAnwer3":"interchange "},{"id":"18 ","question":"The information in this article is ________ inaccurate","trueAnswer":"historic ","falseAnswer1":"historical ","falseAnwser2":"history ","falseAnwer3":"historically"},{"id":" 19 ","question":"My father sometimes ________ the washing up after dinner. ","trueAnswer":"takes ","falseAnswer1":"does ","falseAnwser2":"washes ","falseAnwer3":"makes "},{"id":"20","question":" 500 years ago, the average human ________ was about 40 years","trueAnswer":"lifespan ","falseAnswer1":"lifetime ","falseAnwser2":"life cycle","falseAnwer3":" life length"}]';
final toppicVC4 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"Why don`t they ________ their attention on scrutinizing the evidence instead of questioning the passers-by? ","trueAnswer":"attract ","falseAnswer1":"focus","falseAnwser2":"draw ","falseAnwer3":"devote "},{"id":"2","question":" “Excuse me. Where is the ________ office of OXFAM located?” ","trueAnswer":"head ","falseAnswer1":"Leading","falseAnwser2":"central ","falseAnwer3":"summit "},{"id":"3 ","question":"“All right, it’s true I was nervous”. The leading actor ________ that he had been nervous. ","trueAnswer":"confessed ","falseAnswer1":"apologized ","falseAnwser2":"agreed ","falseAnwer3":"thought "},{"id":"4 ","question":"A nuclear power plant emits less radiation than a granite structure of similar proportion, such as the Lincoln Memorial. “Emits” means ________. ","trueAnswer":"gives off ","falseAnswer1":"concentrates ","falseAnwser2":"repels ","falseAnwer3":"confines "},{"id":"5 ","question":"The United State turns out 16.5 billion hot dog each year. “Turns out” means ________. ","trueAnswer":"produces ","falseAnswer1":"controls ","falseAnwser2":"returns ","falseAnwer3":"delivers "},{"id":"6","question":"The International Red Cross helps people in need without any discrimination based on ________, race, religion, class or political opinions","trueAnswer":"nationality ","falseAnswer1":"nation ","falseAnwser2":"national ","falseAnwer3":"native"},{"id":" 7","question":"How was your exam?---A couple of questions were tricky, but on the _______ it was pretty easy.---- ","trueAnswer":"whole ","falseAnswer1":"spot ","falseAnwser2":"general ","falseAnwer3":"hand "},{"id":"8 ","question":"If you practice regularly, you can learn this language skill in short _______ of a time. ","trueAnswer":"period ","falseAnswer1":"aspect ","falseAnwser2":"arrangement ","falseAnwer3":"activity "},{"id":"9 ","question":"Students can _______ a lot of information just by taking an active part in class. ","trueAnswer":"memorize ","falseAnswer1":"concern ","falseAnwser2":"install ","falseAnwer3":"appear "},{"id":"10 ","question":"I have learned a lot about the value of labour from my _______ at home. ","trueAnswer":"chores ","falseAnswer1":"credit ","falseAnwser2":"energy ","falseAnwer3":"pot plants "},{"id":"11","question":"In the past people believed that women’s _______ roles were as mothers and wives","trueAnswer":"natural ","falseAnswer1":"nature ","falseAnwser2":"naturism ","falseAnwer3":"naturalist "},{"id":"12","question":"A few years ago, a fire _______ much of an overcrowded part of the city. ","trueAnswer":"devastated ","falseAnswer1":"Battled","falseAnwser2":"mopped ","falseAnwer3":"developed "},{"id":"13","question":"Paul Sgmuelson was the first American to won the Nobel Prize in ________. ","trueAnswer":"economics ","falseAnswer1":"economy ","falseAnwser2":"economic ","falseAnwer3":"economical "},{"id":"14 ","question":"How are you____________on with your work? - It’s Ok. ","trueAnswer":"getting ","falseAnswer1":"calling ","falseAnwser2":"laying ","falseAnwer3":"looking "},{"id":"15 ","question":"Spain has little good farmland and lacks many ________ raw materials","trueAnswer":"important industrial ","falseAnswer1":"important industry ","falseAnwser2":"industrious and important ","falseAnwer3":"important industries "},{"id":"16 ","question":"Professional gardeners appreciate flowers for their ________ , gorgeous colors, and pleasant fragrance. ","trueAnswer":"attractive shapes ","falseAnswer1":"attractively shaped","falseAnwser2":"shape and attract ","falseAnwer3":"shaped attractively "},{"id":"17","question":" Jane only makes cakes with the ________ butter. ","trueAnswer":"best unsalted Danish ","falseAnswer1":"unsalted best Danish ","falseAnwser2":"Danish best unsalted ","falseAnwer3":"best Danish unsalted "},{"id":"18","question":" Points will be added to the Entrance Examination scores for those who hold an excellent high school__________. ","trueAnswer":"diploma ","falseAnswer1":"degree ","falseAnwser2":"certificate ","falseAnwer3":"qualification"},{"id":" 19 ","question":"In Vietnam, application forms for the National Entrance Examinations must be __________before the deadline, often in April. ","trueAnswer":"submitted ","falseAnswer1":"filed ","falseAnwser2":"issued ","falseAnwer3":"signed"},{"id":" 20 ","question":"They were among the first companies to exploit the ______ of the Internet. ","trueAnswer":"potential ","falseAnswer1":"prospect ","falseAnwser2":"possibility ","falseAnwer3":"ability"}]';
final toppicVC5 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"My friend tends to look on the bright side in any circumstances.","trueAnswer":"be optimistic ","falseAnswer1":"be smart ","falseAnwser2":"be confident ","falseAnwer3":"be pessimistic "},{"id":"2 ","question":"They decided to postpone their journey till the end of the month because of epidemic. ","trueAnswer":"put off ","falseAnswer1":"turn round ","falseAnwser2":"do with ","falseAnwer3":"carry on "},{"id":"3 ","question":"Most young people nowadays believe in ____ marriage- first comes love, the comes marriage. ","trueAnswer":"romantic ","falseAnswer1":"unique ","falseAnwser2":"contractual ","falseAnwer3":"arranged "},{"id":"4 ","question":"Whenever problems____, we discuss them frankly and find out solutions quickly. ","trueAnswer":"come up ","falseAnswer1":"confide in","falseAnwser2":"believe in ","falseAnwer3":"agree on "},{"id":"5 ","question":"No one can predict the future exactly. Things may happen _________. ","trueAnswer":"unexpectedly","falseAnswer1":"Expectation","falseAnwser2":"expected ","falseAnwer3":"expectedly "},{"id":"6 ","question":"I must tell you about my _________ when I first arrived in London","trueAnswer":"experiences","falseAnswer1":"Incidents","falseAnwser2":"happenings ","falseAnwer3":"events "},{"id":"7 ","question":"The local were not very friendly towards us, in fact there was a distinctly _________ atmosphere. ","trueAnswer":"hostile ","falseAnswer1":"offensive ","falseAnwser2":"rude ","falseAnwer3":"abrupt "},{"id":"8","question":"All the ______ in the stadium applauded the winner of the marathon when he crossed the finishing line. ","trueAnswer":"spectators ","falseAnswer1":"Watchers","falseAnwser2":"audience ","falseAnwer3":"viewers "},{"id":"9","question":" The US president Barack Obama ______ an official visit to Vietnam in May 2016, which is of great significance to the comprehensive bilateral partnership","trueAnswer":"paid ","falseAnswer1":"Delivered","falseAnwser2":"offered ","falseAnwer3":"gave "},{"id":"10 ","question":"The firefighters’ single-minded devotion to the rescue of the victims the fire was ______. ","trueAnswer":"respectable ","falseAnswer1":"respecting ","falseAnwser2":"respective ","falseAnwer3":"respectful "},{"id":"11 ","question":"The university administrations are introducing new measures to ______ that the enrolment process runs smoothly. ","trueAnswer":"ensure ","falseAnswer1":"maintain ","falseAnwser2":"improve ","falseAnwer3":"facilitate "},{"id":"12","question":"With so much _______, I’m lucky to be in work. ","trueAnswer":"unemployment","falseAnswer1":"employees ","falseAnwser2":"employers","falseAnwer3":"employment "},{"id":"13","question":" _______ is a time that is supported to be free from worries. ","trueAnswer":"childhood ","falseAnswer1":"child ","falseAnwser2":"childlike ","falseAnwer3":"childish "},{"id":"14 ","question":"There is a huge amount of _______ associated with children’s TV shows today. ","trueAnswer":"merchandising ","falseAnswer1":"manufacturing ","falseAnwser2":"sales","falseAnwer3":"produce "},{"id":"15","question":" The two countries have reached an agreement through dialogues described as ________. ","trueAnswer":"productive ","falseAnswer1":"counterproductive ","falseAnwser2":"unproductive ","falseAnwer3":"productivity"},{"id":"16 ","question":"The old houses were ______ down to make way for a block of flats.","trueAnswer":"knocked ","falseAnswer1":"banged ","falseAnwser2":"hit ","falseAnwer3":"put"},{"id":" 17","question":" Project-based learning provides wonderful opportunities for students to develop their ______. ","trueAnswer":"creativity ","falseAnswer1":"creative ","falseAnwser2":"create ","falseAnwer3":"creatively "},{"id":"18 ","question":"Violent films may have a negative ______ on children","trueAnswer":"influence ","falseAnswer1":"opinion ","falseAnwser2":"dependence ","falseAnwer3":"decision "},{"id":"19 ","question":"A good leader should not be conservative, but rather ______ to new ideas.","trueAnswer":"receptive ","falseAnswer1":"acceptable ","falseAnwser2":"permissive ","falseAnwer3":"applicable"},{"id":" 20 ","question":"______ individuals are those who share the same hobbies, interests, or points of view. ","trueAnswer":"Like-minded ","falseAnswer1":"Light-hearted ","falseAnwser2":"Even-handed","falseAnwer3":"Open-minded"}]';
final TopicDH1 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word whose capital part differs from the other three in pronunciation in each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"monthS","falseAnswer1":"gloveS","falseAnwser2":"sayS ","falseAnwer3":"singS "},{"id":"2","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word whose capital part differs from the other three in pronunciation in each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"volUntary ","falseAnswer1":"sUmmit ","falseAnwser2":"compUlsory ","falseAnwer3":"Upgrade "},{"id":"3 ","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word that differs from the other three in the position of primary stress in each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"mechanic ","falseAnswer1":"engineer ","falseAnwser2":"understand ","falseAnwer3":"referee "},{"id":"4 ","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word that differs from the other three in the position of primary stress in each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"oceanic","falseAnswer1":"environment ","falseAnwser2":"reality ","falseAnwer3":"psychologist "},{"id":"5","question":"More and more investors are pouring _______ money into food and beverage start-ups. ","trueAnswer":"Ø","falseAnswer1":"the ","falseAnwser2":"a ","falseAnwer3":"an "},{"id":"6","question":"Do you think there _______ less conflict in the world if all people spoke the same language? ","trueAnswer":"would be ","falseAnswer1":"were ","falseAnwser2":"will be ","falseAnwer3":"are "},{"id":"7","question":"Linda rarely goes to school by bike, but today she _______ a bike. ","trueAnswer":"is riding","falseAnswer1":"rides ","falseAnwser2":"is going to ride ","falseAnwer3":"will ride "},{"id":"8","question":"John has worked very late at night these day, _______ he is physically exhauste ","trueAnswer":"so","falseAnswer1":"yet ","falseAnwser2":"hence","falseAnwer3":"because "},{"id":"9","question":"I agree _______ one point with Chris: it will be hard for us to walk 80km. ","trueAnswer":"on ","falseAnswer1":"in ","falseAnwser2":"of ","falseAnwer3":"for "},{"id":"10","question":"_______, the ancient place is still popular with modern tourists. ","trueAnswer":"Built thousands of years ago ","falseAnswer1":"Building thousands of years ago ","falseAnwser2":"It was built thousands of years ago ","falseAnwer3":"To have built thousands of years ago "},{"id":"11","question":" Once _______ in the UK, the book will definitely win a number of awards in regional book fairs. ","trueAnswer":"published","falseAnswer1":"is published ","falseAnwser2":"having published ","falseAnwer3":"publishing "},{"id":"12","question":"Your hair needs _______. You`d better have it done tomorrow. ","trueAnswer":"cutting","falseAnswer1":"cut","falseAnwser2":"to cut ","falseAnwer3":"being cut "},{"id":"13","question":" He was pleased that things were going on _______. ","trueAnswer":"satisfactorily","falseAnswer1":"satisfied","falseAnwser2":"satisfying ","falseAnwer3":"satisfactory"},{"id":"14","question":" Although our opinions on many things _______, we still maintain a good relationship with each other. ","trueAnswer":"differ ","falseAnswer1":"receive ","falseAnwser2":"maintain ","falseAnwer3":"separate "},{"id":"15","question":" Daniel _______ a better understanding of Algebra than we do. ","trueAnswer":"has ","falseAnswer1":"makes","falseAnwser2":"takes ","falseAnwer3":"gives "},{"id":"16","question":"The pointless war between the two countries left thousands of people dead and seriously _______. ","trueAnswer":"wounded","falseAnswer1":"injured ","falseAnwser2":"spoilt ","falseAnwer3":"damaged "},{"id":"17","question":"Eager to be able to discuss my work _______ in French, I hired a tutor to help polish my language skills. ","trueAnswer":"articulately ","falseAnswer1":"expressively ","falseAnwser2":"ambiguously ","falseAnwer3":"understandably "},{"id":"18","question":" The sight of his face brought _______ to me how ill he really was. ","trueAnswer":"home","falseAnswer1":"place","falseAnwser2":"house ","falseAnwer3":"life "},{"id":"-","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word(s) OPPOSITE in meaning to the capital word(s) in each of the following questions.","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"19 ","question":"In a study, more Asian students than American students hold a belief that a husband is OBLIGED to tell his wife his whereabouts if he comes home late. ","trueAnswer":"free ","falseAnswer1":"urged ","falseAnwser2":"required    ","falseAnwer3":"suggested "},{"id":"20","question":"Though I persuaded my boss to solve a very serious problem in the new management system, he just MADE LIGHT OF it. ","trueAnswer":"treated as important","falseAnswer1":"completely ignored ","falseAnwser2":"disagreed with ","falseAnwer3":"discovered by chance "},{"id":"-","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word(s) CLOSET in meaning to the capital word(s) in each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"21","question":"Students from that university have CONDUCTED a survey to find out the most effective study habit. ","trueAnswer":"organized","falseAnswer1":"delayed ","falseAnwser2":"encouraged ","falseAnwer3":"proposed "},{"id":"22","question":"Some operations many have to be halted unless more blood donors COME FORWARD to help. ","trueAnswer":"offer ","falseAnswer1":"claim ","falseAnwser2":"attempt ","falseAnwer3":"refuse "},{"id":"23","question":"Bill is talking to his colleague. Bill: “_______, Jack?” Jack: “Fine! I have just got a promotion.” ","trueAnswer":"How are you doing ","falseAnswer1":"What happened ","falseAnwser2":"What are you doing ","falseAnwer3":"How come"},{"id":"24","question":"Two students are taking in a new class. Student 1: “Excuse me, is anybody sitting here?” Student 2: “_______” ","trueAnswer":"Sorry, the seat is taken. ","falseAnswer1":"No, thanks. ","falseAnwser2":"Yes, I am so gla ","falseAnwer3":"Yes, yes. You can seat here. "},{"id":"25","question":"An earthquake is the result of a sudden release of energy in the Earth`s crust that creates seismic waves. At the Earth`s surface, earthquakes are recognized (25) _______ vibration, shaking and sometimes displacement of the groun The vibrations may vary in (26) _______. They are caused mostly by slippage within geological faults, but also by other events such as volcanic activity, landslides, mine blasts, and nuclear tests. The underground point of (27) _____ of the earthquake is called the focus. The point directly above the focus on the surface is called the epicenter. Earthquakes by themselves rarely kill people or wildlife. It is usually the secondary events (28) _______ they trigger, such as building collapse, fires, tsunamis (seismic sea waves) and volcanoes, that are actually the human disaster. Many of these could possibly be avoided by better construction, safety systems, early warning and (29) _______ planning. ","trueAnswer":"  with","falseAnswer1":" in","falseAnwser2":"    as ","falseAnwer3":" from "},{"id":"26 ","question":"An earthquake is the result of a sudden release of energy in the Earth`s crust that creates seismic waves. At the Earth`s surface, earthquakes are recognized (25) _______ vibration, shaking and sometimes displacement of the groun The vibrations may vary in (26) _______. They are caused mostly by slippage within geological faults, but also by other events such as volcanic activity, landslides, mine blasts, and nuclear tests. The underground point of (27) _____ of the earthquake is called the focus. The point directly above the focus on the surface is called the epicenter. Earthquakes by themselves rarely kill people or wildlife. It is usually the secondary events (28) _______ they trigger, such as building collapse, fires, tsunamis (seismic sea waves) and volcanoes, that are actually the human disaster. Many of these could possibly be avoided by better construction, safety systems, early warning and (29) _______ planning. ","trueAnswer":"  magnitude ","falseAnswer1":"    value ","falseAnwser2":"    amount ","falseAnwer3":" quantity "},{"id":"27","question":"An earthquake is the result of a sudden release of energy in the Earth`s crust that creates seismic waves. At the Earth`s surface, earthquakes are recognized (25) _______ vibration, shaking and sometimes displacement of the groun The vibrations may vary in (26) _______. They are caused mostly by slippage within geological faults, but also by other events such as volcanic activity, landslides, mine blasts, and nuclear tests. The underground point of (27) _____ of the earthquake is called the focus. The point directly above the focus on the surface is called the epicenter. Earthquakes by themselves rarely kill people or wildlife. It is usually the secondary events (28) _______ they trigger, such as building collapse, fires, tsunamis (seismic sea waves) and volcanoes, that are actually the human disaster. Many of these could possibly be avoided by better construction, safety systems, early warning and (29) _______ planning. ","trueAnswer":"origin    ","falseAnswer1":"source ","falseAnwser2":"    center ","falseAnwer3":" epicenter "},{"id":"28","question":"An earthquake is the result of a sudden release of energy in the Earth`s crust that creates seismic waves. At the Earth`s surface, earthquakes are recognized (25) _______ vibration, shaking and sometimes displacement of the groun The vibrations may vary in (26) _______. They are caused mostly by slippage within geological faults, but also by other events such as volcanic activity, landslides, mine blasts, and nuclear tests. The underground point of (27) _____ of the earthquake is called the focus. The point directly above the focus on the surface is called the epicenter. Earthquakes by themselves rarely kill people or wildlife. It is usually the secondary events (28) _______ they trigger, such as building collapse, fires, tsunamis (seismic sea waves) and volcanoes, that are actually the human disaster. Many of these could possibly be avoided by better construction, safety systems, early warning and (29) _______ planning. ","trueAnswer":"  that","falseAnswer1":"who ","falseAnwser2":"    what","falseAnwer3":"those "},{"id":"29","question":"An earthquake is the result of a sudden release of energy in the Earth`s crust that creates seismic waves. At the Earth`s surface, earthquakes are recognized (25) _______ vibration, shaking and sometimes displacement of the groun The vibrations may vary in (26) _______. They are caused mostly by slippage within geological faults, but also by other events such as volcanic activity, landslides, mine blasts, and nuclear tests. The underground point of (27) _____ of the earthquake is called the focus. The point directly above the focus on the surface is called the epicenter. Earthquakes by themselves rarely kill people or wildlife. It is usually the secondary events (28) _______ they trigger, such as building collapse, fires, tsunamis (seismic sea waves) and volcanoes, that are actually the human disaster. Many of these could possibly be avoided by better construction, safety systems, early warning and (29) _______ planning. ","trueAnswer":"evacuation ","falseAnswer1":"evacuator ","falseAnwser2":"evacuate ","falseAnwer3":"evacuating "},{"id":"(Luyện đọc):Read the following passage and mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the correct answer to each of the questions. ","question":"Each year, the Academy Awards, better known as the “Oscars”, celebrate the best films and documentaries with categories ranging from acting, directing and screenwriting, to costumes and special effects. This year, 9-year-old Quvenzhané Wallis joins the list of kids who have taken the movie business by storm, as she competes for the best actress award for her role as „Hushpuppy` in the film “Beasts of the Southern Wild”. (paragraph 2)The Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences is made up of filmmakers in all fields. The group ranks their favorites in each category. Oftentimes Oscar recognition can take many years, but for some lucky and talented individuals that honor comes early in life.(paragraph 3)Newcomer Quvenzhané Wallis (pronounced Kwe-VEN-zhah-nay) portrayed „Hushpuppy,` a young girl fighting to survive in a poor Mississippi Delta community prone to devastating flooding. In the film, Wallis learns to find food in the wilderness, escapes a homeless shelter and deals with the death of her father. She will be the youngest ever nominee in the best actress category at nine years old (paragraph 4)Born in Houma, L, Quvenzhané was just five years old when she auditioned for Beasts of the Southern Wil Since auditions for the role of Hushpuppy were only open to 6-9 year olds, Quvenzhané`s mother lied on the initial paperwork to allow her daughter to audition. When director Benh Zeitlin saw her audition however, he immediately recognized her as the best pick for this strong and independent young character. ","trueAnswer":"_","falseAnswer1":"_","falseAnwser2":"_","falseAnwer3":"_"},{"id":"30","question":"Which of the following is the best title for this passage? ","trueAnswer":"A Young Actress makes it to the Oscars ","falseAnswer1":"Young Actors Achieve Big for the Oscars ","falseAnwser2":"Little Lady Nominees for the Oscars ","falseAnwer3":"Youngest Ever Nominee for the Oscars "},{"id":"31","question":"Which of the following is NOT celebrated by the Academy Awards? ","trueAnswer":"news ","falseAnswer1":"films ","falseAnwser2":"documentaries","falseAnwer3":"cartoons "},{"id":"32","question":"The phrase “that honor” in paragraph 2 refers to _______. ","trueAnswer":"Oscars recognition ","falseAnswer1":"lucky and talented individuals","falseAnwser2":"favorites ","falseAnwer3":"award "},{"id":"33","question":"Which of the following best describe Quvenzhané Wallis according to the passage?","trueAnswer":"She is the youngest ever nominee in the best actress category for the Oscars.  ","falseAnswer1":"She is a young girl fighting to survive in a poor Mississippi Delta community. ","falseAnwser2":"She has won the best actress Oscars award for her role in “Hushpuppy”. ","falseAnwer3":"She escapes a homeless shelter and deals with the death of her father. "},{"id":"34","question":"Which of the following best paraphrases the clause “who have taken the movie business by storm” in the reading? ","trueAnswer":"who have been particularly successful in the movie business ","falseAnswer1":"who have earned their living in the movie business ","falseAnwser2":"who have made huge profits in the movie business ","falseAnwer3":"who have recovered from a difficult period in the movie business "},{"id":"(Luyện đọc):Read the following passage and mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the correct answer to each of the questions. ","question":"No sooner had the first intrepid male aviators safely returned to Earth than it seemed that women, too, had been smitten by an urge to fly. From mere spectators, they became willing passengers and finally pilots in their own right, plotting their skills and daring line against the hazards of the air and the skepticism of their male counterparts. In doing so they enlarged the traditional bounds of a women`s world, won for their sex a new sense of competence and achievement, and contributed handsomely to the progress of aviation.But recognition of their abilities did not come easily.``Men do not believe us capable.``the famed aviator Amelia Earhart once remarked to a frien ``Because we are women, seldom are we trusted to do an efficient jo`` Indeed, old attitudes died hard: when Charles Lindbergh visited the Soviet Union in 1938 with his wife, Anne-herself a pilot and gifted proponent of aviation - he was astonished to discover both men and women flying in the Soviet Air Force.Such conventional wisdom made it difficult for women to raise money for the up - to - date equipment they needed to compete on an equal basis with men. Yet they did compete, and often they triumphed finally despite the odds. Ruth Law, whose 590 - mile flight from Chicago to Hornell, New York, set a new nonstop distance record in 1916, exemplified the resourcefulness and grit demanded of any woman who wanted to fly. And when she addressed the Aero Club of America after completing her historic journey, her plainspoken words testified to a universal human motivation that was unaffected by gender: ``My flight was done with no expectation of reward,`` she declared, ``just purely for the love of accomplishment.`` ","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"35","question":"Which of the following is the best title for this passage? ","trueAnswer":"Women in Aviation History ","falseAnswer1":"Long Flight ","falseAnwser2":"Dangers Faced by Pilots ","falseAnwer3":"Women Spectators "},{"id":"36","question":"According to the passage, women pilots were successful in all of the following EXCEPT _______. ","trueAnswer":"winning universal recognition from men","falseAnswer1":"challenging the conventional role of women","falseAnwser2":" contributing to the science of aviation ","falseAnwer3":"  building the confidence of women "},{"id":"37","question":"What can be inferred from the passage about the United States Air Force in 1938? ","trueAnswer":"  It had no women pilots.","falseAnswer1":"It gave pilots handsome salaries. ","falseAnwser2":"    It had old planes that were in need of repair. ","falseAnwer3":" It could not be trusted to do an efficient jo "},{"id":"38","question":"In their efforts to compete with men, early women pilots had difficulty in _______. ","trueAnswer":"  raising money ","falseAnswer1":"addressing clubs ","falseAnwser2":"flying nonstop ","falseAnwer3":"setting records "},{"id":"39","question":" According to the passage, who said that flying was done with no expectation of reward? ","trueAnswer":"Ruth Law ","falseAnswer1":"Amelia Earhart ","falseAnwser2":"Charles Lindbergh ","falseAnwer3":" Anne Lindbergh "},{"id":"40","question":"The word “skepticism” is closest in meaning to _______. ","trueAnswer":"  doubt ","falseAnswer1":"hatred ","falseAnwser2":"    support ","falseAnwer3":"surprise"},{"id":"41","question":" The word “addressed” can be best replaced by _______. ","trueAnswer":"spoke to ","falseAnswer1":"mailed ","falseAnwser2":"came back to ","falseAnwer3":"consulted "},{"id":"42","question":" The word “counterparts” refers to _______. ","trueAnswer":"pilots","falseAnswer1":"passengers ","falseAnwser2":"skills ","falseAnwer3":" hazards "},{"id":"-","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the underlined part that needs correction in each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"43","question":" Some people say often that using cars is not so convenient as using motorbikes. ","trueAnswer":"   say often","falseAnswer1":"     using cars","falseAnwser2":"     so","falseAnwer3":"  as using motorbikes"},{"id":"44","question":" They are having their house being painted by a construction company. ","trueAnswer":"   being painted","falseAnswer1":"     having","falseAnwser2":"     their","falseAnwer3":"  construction"},{"id":"45","question":"Transgender people are denied the ability to join the armed forces due to discriminating policies implemented by the government. ","trueAnswer":"   discriminating","falseAnswer1":"     Transgender","falseAnwser2":"     are denied","falseAnwer3":"  armed forces"},{"id":"-","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the sentence that is closest in meaning to each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"46","question":"“If I hadn`t had so much work to do, I would have gone to the movies.” said the boy. ","trueAnswer":"   They boy said that if he hadn`t had so much work to do, he would have gone to the movies. ","falseAnswer1":"     As the boy did not have much work to do, he went to the movies. ","falseAnwser2":"     The boy explained the reason why he had so much work to do that he couldn`t go to the movies. ","falseAnwer3":"  The boy didn`t want to go to the movies because he did have so much to do. "},{"id":"47","question":"If only you told me the truth about the theft. ","trueAnswer":"   You should have told me the truth about the theft. ","falseAnswer1":"     I do wish you would tell me the truth about the theft. ","falseAnwser2":"     You must have told me the truth about the theft. ","falseAnwer3":"  It is necessary that you tell me the truth about the theft. "},{"id":"48","question":"The demand was so great that they had to reprint the book immediately. ","trueAnswer":"   So great was the demand that they had to print the book immediately. ","falseAnswer1":"     They had to print the book immediately to satisfy the increasing deman ","falseAnwser2":"     To meet the greater and greater demand, they had to print the book immediately. ","falseAnwer3":"  There was such a great demand that the book was printed immediately. "},{"id":"-","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the sentence that best combines each pair of sentences in the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"49","question":"Julian dropped out of college after his first year. Now he regrets it. ","trueAnswer":"   Julian regrets having dropped out of college after his first year.","falseAnswer1":"     Julian regretted having dropped out of college after his first year. ","falseAnwser2":" Julian wishes he didn`t drop out of college after his first year. ","falseAnwer3":"  Only if Julian had dropped out of college after his first year. "},{"id":"50","question":"Seth informed us of his retirement from the company. He did it when arriving at the meeting. ","trueAnswer":"   No sooner had Seth arrived at the meeting than we were told about his leaving the company.","falseAnswer1":"     Only after his retiring from the company did Seth tell us about his arrival at the meeting. ","falseAnwser2":"     Not until Seth said to us that he would leave the company did he turn up at the meeting. ", "falseAnwer3":"  Hardly had Seth notified us of his retiring from the company when he arrived at the meeting. "}]';
final TopicDH2 =
    '[{"id":"1","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C, or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word that differs from the other three in the position of primary stress in each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"danger ","falseAnswer1":"enroll ","falseAnwser2":"promote ","falseAnwer3":"require "},{"id":"2","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C, or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word that differs from the other three in the position of primary stress in each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"optimistic ","falseAnswer1":" diversity ","falseAnwser2":"environment","falseAnwer3":" assimilate "},{"id":"3","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word whose capital part differs from the other three in pronunciation in each of the following questions.. ","trueAnswer":"influencED","falseAnswer1":"     terrifiED ","falseAnwser2":" averaged","falseAnwer3":"  accompaniED "},{"id":"4","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word whose capital part differs from the other three in pronunciation in each of the following questions.. ","trueAnswer":"applIcant ","falseAnswer1":"Identify ","falseAnwser2":"fInal  ","falseAnwer3":"decIde "},{"id":"-","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C, or D on your answer sheet to indicate the underlined part that needs correction in each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"5","question":" He bought a lot of books, none of them he has ever readread","trueAnswer":"   them","falseAnswer1":"     Bought","falseAnwser2":"     none of    ","falseAnwer3":" has ever read"},{"id":"6","question":"There is a few evidence that the children in language classrooms learn foreign languages any better than adults in similar classroom situation. ","trueAnswer":"few evidence","falseAnswer1":"in language classrooms  ","falseAnwser2":"better","falseAnwer3":"classroom situation"},{"id":"7","question":"The theory isn`t sounding persuasive anymore because it has been opposed by many scholars. ","trueAnswer":"   isn`t sounding","falseAnswer1":"     anymore","falseAnwser2":"     has been opposed","falseAnwer3":"  scholars"},{"id":"8","question":" The babysitter has told Billy`s parents about his _______ behavior and how he starts acting as soon as they leave home. ","trueAnswer":"attention-seeking     ","falseAnswer1":"     focus-seeking ","falseAnwser2":"     meditation-seeking     ","falseAnwer3":"concentration-seeking "},{"id":"9","question":"_______as a masterpiece, a work of art must transcend the ideals of the period in which it was create ","trueAnswer":"   To be ranked   ","falseAnswer1":" In order to be ranking     ","falseAnwser2":"     Ranking ","falseAnwer3":"  Being ranked "},{"id":"10","question":"Every _______ piece of equipment was sent to the fire. ","trueAnswer":"   disposable" ,"falseAnswer1":"     consumable ","falseAnwser2":"     spendable ","falseAnwer3":"  available "},{"id":"11","question":"Smith had a lucky escape. He _______ kille ","trueAnswer":"could have been ","falseAnswer1":"     shouldn`t have been ","falseAnwser2":"     should have been ","falseAnwer3":"  must have been     "},{"id":"12","question":" Neither of the boys came to school yesterday, __________?","trueAnswer":"   did they ","falseAnswer1":"     didn`t they ","falseAnwser2":"     does they ","falseAnwer3":"  doesn`t they "},{"id":"13","question":"A good leader in globalization is not to impose but change. ","trueAnswer":"   facilitate ","falseAnswer1":"     show ","falseAnwser2":"     cause  ","falseAnwer3":" oppose "},{"id":"14","question":"The old man warned the young boys _______ in the deep river. ","trueAnswer":"   against swimming ","falseAnswer1":"     not to swimming ","falseAnwser2":"     don`t swim ","falseAnwer3":"  to swim "},{"id":"15","question":"His father used to be a _______ professor at the university. Many students worshipped him. ","trueAnswer":"distinguished  ","falseAnswer1":"distinguishing ","falseAnwser2":"     distinct ","falseAnwer3":"  distinctive    "},{"id":"16","question":" If Tim _______ so fast, his car wouldn`t have crashed into a tree. ","trueAnswer":"   hadn`t driven ","falseAnswer1":"     haven`t driven ","falseAnwser2":"     didn`t drive ","falseAnwer3":"  drives "},{"id":"17","question":"Most of the_______ in this workshop do not work very seriously or productively. ","trueAnswer":"   rank and file ","falseAnswer1":"     tooth and nail ","falseAnwser2":"     eager beavers ","falseAnwer3":"  old hands "},{"id":"18","question":"Not only _______ in the field of psychology but animal behavior is examined as well. ","trueAnswer":"   is human behavior studied ","falseAnswer1":"     is studied human behavior ","falseAnwser2":"     human behavior ","falseAnwer3":"human behavior is studied "},{"id":"19","question":"Luckily, the rain ______ so we were able to play the match. ","trueAnswer":"held off ","falseAnswer1":"     watered down","falseAnwser2":"     gave out ","falseAnwer3":"  got away   "},{"id":"-","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C, or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word(s) CLOSEST in meaning to the capital word(s) in each of the following questions.","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"20","question":"Technological changes have rendered many traditional skill OBSOLETE. ","trueAnswer":"outdated ","falseAnswer1":"     impractical ","falseAnwser2":"     unappreciated ","falseAnwer3":"  undeveloped "},{"id":"21","question":"By being THRIFTY and shopping wisely, housewives in the city can feed an entire family on as little as 500.000 VND a week. ","trueAnswer":"   economical ","falseAnswer1":"     luxurious ","falseAnwser2":"     sensible ","falseAnwer3":"  miserable "},{"id":"-","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C, or D on your answer sheet to indicate the word(s) OPPOSITE in meaning to the capital word(s) in each of the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"22","question":"Research suggests that children are more RESILIENT than adults when it comes to getting over an illness. ","trueAnswer":"making a slow recovery     ","falseAnswer1":"becoming much stronger ","falseAnwser2":"     becoming healthy again ","falseAnwer3":"      making a quick recovery "},{"id":"23","question":"Blue is AN OLD HAND at such compositions and has never had any trouble with them. ","trueAnswer":"inexperienced in","falseAnswer1":"     relaxed about ","falseAnwser2":"     reserved about ","falseAnwer3":"  uninterested in "},{"id":"24","question":"Tony and Bob are talking in their classroom. - Tony: “We are buying Lily a graduation present.”- Bob:” _______” ","trueAnswer":"   Could I chip in? ","falseAnswer1":"     She`s out of my league. ","falseAnwser2":"     Can you all be more down-to-earth? ","falseAnwer3":"  I`m ranking in money now. "},{"id":"25","question":"Mai and Joey are talking about their favorite pastimes. - Joey: “ What sort of things do you like doing in your free time?”- Mai: “_______” ","trueAnswer":"   I love checking out the shops for new clothes. ","falseAnswer1":"     None. Been starved since 9 yesterday. ","falseAnwser2":"     I hate shopping. ","falseAnwer3":"  Nothing special. Just some photos I took on the trip to Nepal. "},{"id":"26","question":"Urbanisation programmes are being carried out in many parts of the world, especially in densely (26) ________ regions with limited land and resources. It is the natural outcome of economic development and industrialisation. It has brought a lot of benefits to our society. However, it also (27) ________ various problems for local authorities and town planners in the process of maintaining sustainable urbanization, especially in developing countries. When too many people cram into a small area, urban infrastructure can`t be effective. There will be a (28) ________ of livable housing, energy and water supply. This will create overcrowded urban districts with no proper facilities. Currently, fast urbanization is taking place predominantly in developing countries where sustainable urbanization has little relevance to people`s lives. Their houses are just shabby slums with poor sanitation. Their children only manage to get basic education. Hence, the struggle for (29) ________ is their first priority rather than anything else. Only when the quality of their existence is improved, can they seek (30) ________ other high values in their life.  ","trueAnswer":"popular ","falseAnswer1":" populated ","falseAnwser2":"     crowed ","falseAnwer3":"  numerous "},{"id":"27","question":"Urbanisation programmes are being carried out in many parts of the world, especially in densely (26) ________ regions with limited land and resources. It is the natural outcome of economic development and industrialisation. It has brought a lot of benefits to our society. However, it also (27) ________ various problems for local authorities and town planners in the process of maintaining sustainable urbanization, especially in developing countries. When too many people cram into a small area, urban infrastructure can`t be effective. There will be a (28) ________ of livable housing, energy and water supply. This will create overcrowded urban districts with no proper facilities. Currently, fast urbanization is taking place predominantly in developing countries where sustainable urbanization has little relevance to people`s lives. Their houses are just shabby slums with poor sanitation. Their children only manage to get basic education. Hence, the struggle for (29) ________ is their first priority rather than anything else. Only when the quality of their existence is improved, can they seek (30) ________ other high values in their life. ","trueAnswer":"   poses ","falseAnswer1":"     offers ","falseAnwser2":"     leads ","falseAnwer3":"  imposes "},{"id":"28","question":"Urbanisation programmes are being carried out in many parts of the world, especially in densely (26) ________ regions with limited land and resources. It is the natural outcome of economic development and industrialisation. It has brought a lot of benefits to our society. However, it also (27) ________ various problems for local authorities and town planners in the process of maintaining sustainable urbanization, especially in developing countries. When too many people cram into a small area, urban infrastructure can`t be effective. There will be a (28) ________ of livable housing, energy and water supply. This will create overcrowded urban districts with no proper facilities. Currently, fast urbanization is taking place predominantly in developing countries where sustainable urbanization has little relevance to people`s lives. Their houses are just shabby slums with poor sanitation. Their children only manage to get basic education. Hence, the struggle for (29) ________ is their first priority rather than anything else. Only when the quality of their existence is improved, can they seek (30) ________ other high values in their life. ","trueAnswer":"lack  ","falseAnswer1":"appearance ","falseAnwser2":"plenty ","falseAnwer3":"loss "},{"id":"29","question":"Urbanisation programmes are being carried out in many parts of the world, especially in densely (26) ________ regions with limited land and resources. It is the natural outcome of economic development and industrialisation. It has brought a lot of benefits to our society. However, it also (27) ________ various problems for local authorities and town planners in the process of maintaining sustainable urbanization, especially in developing countries. When too many people cram into a small area, urban infrastructure can`t be effective. There will be a (28) ________ of livable housing, energy and water supply. This will create overcrowded urban districts with no proper facilities. Currently, fast urbanization is taking place predominantly in developing countries where sustainable urbanization has little relevance to people`s lives. Their houses are just shabby slums with poor sanitation. Their children only manage to get basic education. Hence, the struggle for (29) ________ is their first priority rather than anything else. Only when the quality of their existence is improved, can they seek (30) ________ other high values in their life. ","trueAnswer":"survival","falseAnswer1":"     Survive    ","falseAnwser2":" survivor ","falseAnwer3":"  survived "},{"id":"30","question":"Urbanisation programmes are being carried out in many parts of the world, especially in densely (26) ________ regions with limited land and resources. It is the natural outcome of economic development and industrialisation. It has brought a lot of benefits to our society. However, it also (27) ________ various problems for local authorities and town planners in the process of maintaining sustainable urbanization, especially in developing countries. When too many people cram into a small area, urban infrastructure can`t be effective. There will be a (28) ________ of livable housing, energy and water supply. This will create overcrowded urban districts with no proper facilities. Currently, fast urbanization is taking place predominantly in developing countries where sustainable urbanization has little relevance to people`s lives. Their houses are just shabby slums with poor sanitation. Their children only manage to get basic education. Hence, the struggle for (29) ________ is their first priority rather than anything else. Only when the quality of their existence is improved, can they seek (30) ________ other high values in their life. ","trueAnswer":"for","falseAnswer1":"     about ","falseAnwser2":"     with ","falseAnwer3":"  on "},{"id":"(Luyện đọc): Read the following passage and mark the letter A, B, C, or D on your answer sheet to indicate the correct answer to each of the questions from 31 to 38. ","question":"(paragraph 1)Let children learn to judge their own work. A child learning to talk does not learn by being corrected all the time. If corrected too much, he will stop talking. He notices a thousand times a day the difference between the language he uses and the language those around him use. Bit by bit, he makes the necessary changes to make his language like other people`s. In the same way, children learn all the other things they learn to do without being taught – to talk, run, climb, whistle, ride a bicycle – compare their own performances with those of more skilled people, and slowly make the needed changes. But in school we never give a child a chance to find out his mistakes for himself, let alone correct them. We do it all for him. We act as if we thought that he would never notice a mistake unless it was pointed out to him, or correct it unless he was made to. Soon he becomes dependent on the teacher. Let him do it himself. Let him work out, with the help of other children if he wants it, what this word says, what the answer is to that problem, whether this is a good way of saying or doing this or not. (paragraph 2)If it is a matter of right answers, as it may be in mathematics or science, give him the answer book. Let him correct his own papers. Why should we teachers waste time on such routine work? Our job should be to help the child when he tells us that he can`t find the way to get the right answer. Let`s end all this nonsense of grades, exams, and marks. Let us throw them all out, and let the children learn what all educated persons must someday learn, how to measure their own understanding, how to know what they know or do not know.(paragraph 3)Let them get on with this job in the way that seems most sensible to them, with our help as school teachers if they ask for it. The idea that there is a body of knowledge to be learnt at school and used for the rest of one`s life is nonsense in a world as complicated and rapidly changing as ours. Anxious parents and teachers say, “But suppose they fail to learn something essential, something they will need to get on in the world?” Don`t worry! If it is essential, they will go out into the world and learn it. ","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"31","question":"What does the author think is the best way for children to learn things? ","trueAnswer":"By copying what other people do","falseAnswer1":"     By listening to explanations from skilled people  ","falseAnwser2":"     By asking a great many questions ","falseAnwer3":"  By making mistakes and having them corrected "},{"id":"32","question":"The passage suggests that learning to speak and learning to ride a bicycle are _______. ","trueAnswer":"   basically the same as learning other skills ","falseAnswer1":"     basically different from learning adult skills ","falseAnwser2":"     not really important skills ","falseAnwer3":"  more important than other skills "},{"id":"33","question":"What does the author think teachers do which they should not do? ","trueAnswer":"   They point out children`s mistakes to them ","falseAnswer1":"     They give children correct answers ","falseAnwser2":"     They allow children to mark their own work ","falseAnwer3":"  They encourage children to copy from one another "},{"id":"34","question":" The word “those” in paragraph 1 refers to ___________. ","trueAnswer":"people","falseAnswer1":"skills  ","falseAnwser2":" changes ","falseAnwer3":"  things "},{"id":" 35","question":"According to paragraph 1, what basic skills do children learn to do without being taught?","trueAnswer":"   Talking, climbing and whistling ","falseAnswer1":"     Reading, talking and hearing","falseAnwser2":"     Running, walking and playing ","falseAnwer3":"  Talking, running and skiing "},{"id":"36","question":"Exams, grades and marks should be abolished because children`s progress should only be estimated by __________. ","trueAnswer":"   the children themselves","falseAnswer1":"     Parents","falseAnwser2":"     educated persons ","falseAnwer3":"  teachers "},{"id":"37","question":" The word “essential” in paragraph 3 is closest in meaning to ___________. ","trueAnswer":"   important ","falseAnswer1":"     wonderful ","falseAnwser2":"     complicated    ","falseAnwer3":" difficult"},{"id":"38","question":"The author fears that children will grow up into adults who are ___________. ","trueAnswer":"unable to think for themselves","falseAnswer1":"     too critical of themselves ","falseAnwser2":"     unable to use basic skills ","falseAnwer3":"  too independent of others "},{"id":"(Luyện đọc):Read the following passage and mark the letter A, B, C, or D on your answer sheet to indicate the correct answer to each of the questions from 39 to 43. ","question":"(paragraph 1)Accidents do not occur at random. People eighty-five years of age and older are twenty-two times likely to die accidentally than are children five to nine years ol The risk for native Americans is four times that for Asian-Americans and twice that for white Americans or African-Americans. Males suffer accidents at more than twice the rate of females, in part because they are more prone to risky behavior. Alaskans are more than three times as likely as Rhode Islanders to die in an accident. Texans are twenty-one times more likely than New Jerseyites to die in a natural disaster. Among the one hundred most populous counties, kern County, California (Bakersfield), has an accident fatality rate three times greater than Summit County, Ohio (Akron).( paragraph 2) Accidents happens more often to poor people. Those living in poverty receive inferior medical care, are more apt to reside in houses with faulty heating and electrical systems, drive older cars with fewer safety features, and are less likely to use safety belts. People in rural areas have more accidents than city or suburban dwellers because farming is much riskier than working in a factory or office and because emergency medical services are less readily available. These two factors – low income and rural residence – may explain why the south has a higher accident rate than the north. ","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"39","question":"Which of the following is TRUE according to the passage? ","trueAnswer":"   The risk of having an accident is greater among certain groups of people. ","falseAnswer1":"     Children aged five to nine face the greatest accident risk. ","falseAnwser2":"     All people face an equal risk of having an accident. ","falseAnwer3":"  One in every 22 people aged 85 and over will die in an accident. "},{"id":"40","question":"The word ``inferior`` in the passage is closest in meaning to ______. ","trueAnswer":"   low-quality","falseAnswer1":"     modern     ","falseAnwser2":" well-equipped ","falseAnwer3":"  unsafe "},{"id":"41","question":"According to the passage, which of the following groups of people in America face the highest risk of having an accident? ","trueAnswer":"   Native Americans ","falseAnswer1":"     Asian-Americans ","falseAnwser2":"     White Americans ","falseAnwer3":"  African-Americans "},{"id":"42","question":"What does the word ``that`` in the passage refer to? ","trueAnswer":"   the risk ","falseAnswer1":"     Males","falseAnwser2":"     native Americans ","falseAnwer3":"  Afirican-Americans "},{"id":"43","question":"Which of the following is NOT mentioned as a reason for a higher accident rate among the poor? ","trueAnswer":"   Little knowledge about safety ","falseAnswer1":"     Inadequate medical services ","falseAnwser2":"     Poor housing and working conditions ","falseAnwer3":"  Use of cars which incorporate fewer safety features "},{"id":"-","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C, or D on your answer sheet to indicate the sentence that is closest in meaning to each of the following questions.","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"- "},{"id":"44","question":"It was not until after I got home that I realized I had not set the burglar alarm in the office. ","trueAnswer":"   I didn`t turn the burglar alarm on before I left the office, but I only became aware of this after I`d arrive home. ","falseAnswer1":"     Fortunately, I realized that I hadn`t set the burglar alarm just before I left for home; otherwise, I would have had to travel all the way back to the office. ","falseAnwser2":"     On the way home, I suddenly realized that I had forgotten to turn on the burglar alarm in the office. ","falseAnwer3":"  I wish I had realized before I arrived home that I hadn`t turn on the burglar alarm in the office, then it would have been easier to go and set it. "},{"id":"45","question":" Phil wanted to be separated from his family on the business trip for less time than he was on the last.","trueAnswer":"On this business trip, Phil hoped that he would not be away from his family for as long a time as he had been on the previous one.  ","falseAnswer1":"     As he had enjoyed being away from his family for such a long time on his last business trip, Phil hoped that this trip would be even longer. ","falseAnwser2":"     Phil knew that the business trip he was soon to take would keep him away from his family for less time than the previous one. ","falseAnwer3":"  No longer wanting to take lengthy business trips because they separated him from his family, Phil preferred not to go on any at all. "},{"id":"46","question":" When there is so much traffic on the roads, it is sometimes quicker to walk than to go by car. ","trueAnswer":"It is faster to walk than to drive in the heavy traffic at certain time of the day. ","falseAnswer1":"     The traffic is always so heavy that you`d better walk to work; it`s quicker. ","falseAnwser2":"     There is so much traffic these days that it is more pleasant to walk than to drive. ","falseAnwer3":"  During rush hours, walking gives me much more pleasure than driving in the heavy traffi "},{"id":"47","question":"I`m like my mum, whereas my brother looks like my dad ","trueAnswer":"   I`m like my mum, whereas my brother takes after my dad ","falseAnswer1":"     I`m like my mum, whereas my brother takes over my dad ","falseAnwser2":"     I`m like my mum, whereas my brother takes on my dad ","falseAnwer3":"  I`m like my mum, whereas my brother takes in my da "},{"id":"-","question":"Mark the letter A, B, C, or D on your answer sheet to indicate the sentence that best combines each pair of sentences in the following questions. ","trueAnswer":"-","falseAnswer1":"-","falseAnwser2":"-","falseAnwer3":"-"},{"id":"48","question":"You don`t try to work har You will fail in the exam.","trueAnswer":"   Unless you try to work hard, you will fail in the exam.  ","falseAnswer1":"     Unless you don`t try to work hard, you will fail in the exam. ","falseAnwser2":"     Unless you try to work hard, you won`t fail in the exam. ","falseAnwer3":"  Unless do you try to work hard, you will fail in the exam. "},{"id":"49","question":" Marry loved her stuffed animal when she was young. She couldn`t sleep without it. ","trueAnswer":"When Marry was young, she loved her stuffed animal so much that she couldn`t sleep without it. ","falseAnswer1":"     When Mary was young, she loved her stuffed animal so as not to sleep without it.","falseAnwser2":"     As Marry couldn`t sleep without her stuffed animal when she was young, she loved it. ","falseAnwer3":"  When Marry was young, she loved her stuffed animal though she couldn`t sleep without it. "},{"id":"50","question":"``Cigarette?``, he sai ``No, thanks.`` I said","trueAnswer":"   He offered me a cigarette, but I promptly decline ","falseAnswer1":"     He asked for a cigarette, and I immediately refuse ","falseAnwser2":"     He mentioned a cigarette, so I thanked him. ","falseAnwer3":"  He asked if I was smoking, and I denied at once."}]';
